-我能再续一杯吗 -行
- Can I get another refill? - Yes.
那我能知道为什么这附近没有牲畜
Can I get an explanation of why you're wearing overalls
你却穿着那乡下工装裤吗
when there are no goats around?
哎哟 还不止
Oh, wait...
他还打起鼓来了
Now he's drumming.
乡下工装裤 蹭免费续杯 还敲敲打打
Overalls, free coffee refills, and drumming.
众里寻他千百度
We can stop looking.
全世界最惹人厌的嬉皮士就在本店椅子处
We found the world's most annoying hipster.
麦克斯 这不是阿憨餐厅
Max, this isn't a diner
能随便有恶劣态度与大肠杆菌
where everything comes with attitude and ecoli.
这里是小蛋糕店
This is the cupcake shop.
你是这里的老板呢
You own this place.
成功的代价就是得当孙子[被切蛋蛋]啊
Ugh, success really cuts your balls off!
我们懂了 你部落有麻烦是吧
We get it. Your tribe's in trouble.
她开玩笑而已啦
Hey, she's kidding.
欢迎去续杯您的杏仁摩卡
Just help yourself to a fresh mocha almond refill.
对了 你节奏超摇摆啊
And by the way, sick beats.
你还给他比划个和平手势啊
You threw him a peace sign?
你以为你谁啊 小日本青年咩
What are you, a japanese teenager?
只是表达友善的手势嘛
It's a gesture of goodwill.
行 但你要让我看到你用手比心
Okay, but if I see you doing an open heart,
老娘一定杀了你
I will kill you.
是安迪呢
Hey, there's Andy.
我不想他看到我
I don't want him to see me.
你就这么大喇喇地跟我前男友打招呼吗
Did you just openly wave to my ex-boyfriend?
对啊 我每次都会打招呼
Yeah, I always wave at him.
他又没因为
He didn't die just because
你不给他摸奶就变成死人
you stopped letting him touch your boobies.
但我就不会跟你睡过的唱片行店员
Well, I don't wave to the guy at the record shop
打招呼啊
that you had sex with.
我有睡过那唱片行店员啊
I had sex with the guy at the record shop?
我真应该写日记记录下
I should keep a diary.
天啊 他要折回来了
Oh, God, he's coming back.
瞧你手贱惹来的事
See what you started with your wave?
抱歉 我的手超友善啊
I'm sorry. My hand is friendly.
跟我"有过一手"的高中男同学都知道
Ask any guy in high school.
我本来是想偷偷溜来的
I was gonna try and sneak by,
不过那样太幼稚了
but that just seemed so juvenile,
所以呢 "你们还喜欢我吗"
so here, "Do you guys still like me?
请勾选是或否
Check 'yes' or 'no.'"
她还好吗
So how's she doing?
-很好啦 -真的吗
- She's good. - Really?
对了 唱片行那男的让我替他问好
Oh, by the way, the guy at the record store says hi.
那你替我问他 "你是哪根葱啊"
Well, you tell him I said, "who are you?"
我来还有另一个原因呢 麦克斯
And I also came in because I wanted to make sure
我想确认我们俩友谊不变
everything's cool with you and me, Max.
你已经有48小时
I mean, you haven't texted me a pic
没有发给我非比寻常的动物友情图了
of an unlikely animal friendship in, like, 48 hours.
别担心 我们友谊不变
Don't worry, we're cool.
我只是还没找到能赢过
I just haven't been able to top the picture I sent
猴子挠鹦鹉的新图而已
of the monkey tickling a parrot.
我明白 你的标准超高
I get it. You have high standards.
而我是只要看到一只黑狗抱着一只棕狗
Whereas, me, I see a black dog spooning a brown dog,
就达到我标准了
and I pull the trigger.
那种低档烂图留给你娘看吧
Well, save that amateur crap for your mom,
说不定再副本抄送叔叔阿姨
perhaps with an aunt and uncle cc.
完全就是我会干的事
Ha, that is so me.
大师 你把标准拉高了
Well, sir, you have raised the bar.
我很期待下一张怪异又有爱的动物图哦
I look forward to our next freaky/adorable animal pic.
你也在想我想着的事吗
Well, are you thinking what I'm thinking?
我跟他分手后 他变胖了
Since we broke up, he got fat.
你们才分手四天好吗
It's only been four days.
薇诺娜·贾德一小时就能胖呢
Wynonna Judd gets fat in an hour.
我已经累到没力气想他的事了
I'm too exhausted to even think about Andy.
我们赶紧换衣服去餐厅吧
Let's just change and get to the diner.
我们只需要再坚持个八小时
Look, all we have to do is make it through eight more hours,
我们就能回家睡大觉了
and then we can get a good night's sleep.
麦克斯 你居然在公众场合脱裤子
Max, you're taking your pants off in public!
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
我太累了 都忘了我在哪
I'm so tired, I forgot where I was!
裤子都脱一半了 我该怎么办
They're halfway down. What do I do?
我累到没力气决定了
I'm too tired to make the call.
来一份培根生菜三明治加薯条
And I'll have the BLT with the french fries.
小姐 我们的服务员好像睡着了
Miss? I think our waitress is asleep.
是啊 她很累 我们最近很缺觉
Yeah, she's tired. We haven't slept a lot lately.
等她醒了 就会帮你们点单
When she wakes up, she'll take your order.
-但我们已经很饿了 -少烦她
- But we're really hungry... - Leave her alone!
我有在你上班时去叫醒过你吗
So I come to your job and wake you up?
您好 准备好点单了吗
Hi, can I take your order?
麦克斯 我看得出你有多累
I can see how tired you are, Max.
如果我能把时光倒回75那会儿
and if I could turn the clock back to '75,
我肯定会帮你搞点毒品助眠
I'd help you out with a nice bump of cocaine.
但我已经金盆洗手了
But I don't do that anymore.
厄尔 你1975年就戒毒啦
Earl, you quit coke in 1975?
不 是去年 我75岁那会
No, when I was 75, last year.
岁月不饶人啊
It just felt like time.
现在我只能给你击拳鼓舞士气了
Now all I can give you is a nice bump of this.
麦克斯 有件事我想你解释一下
Max, I need you to explain something to me
我实在百思不得其解啊
'cause I can't figure it out.
你占据身体9成比例的大头 居然也想不出吗
That's hard to believe, since you're 90% head.
这事不好笑好吗 麦克斯
It's not a laughing matter, Max.
当年我出世 我妈骨盆都裂了
I broke my mother's pelvis coming out.
千呼万唤始出世[出柜]啊
At least you finally came out.
所以你够精神吐槽你老板
Oh, so you're awake enough to ridicule the boss,
可是不够精神去端菜点单吗
but not awake enough to wait on tables.
没错 你的大脑袋还是有用的嘛
Exactly. See, there's that big head working.
而且别小题大做好吗
And don't exaggerate.
卡洛琳跟我干活可好了
Caroline and I are doing a great job.
-醒醒 -您好 准备好点单了吗
- Wake up. - Hi, can I take your order?
我只知道如果我干活像
All I know is if I was doing my job
你俩今晚这么烂的话
as bad as you two tonight,
我早自尽去了
I'd take my own life.
你还是有机会的
That's not off the table.
行啦 阿憨 放我们一马吧
Come on, Han, cut us a break.
我们有两份工 一天只能睡两小时
We're working two jobs, we got two hours of sleep.
我们只想回家睡大觉
We just want to get home and climb into bed.
你们睡一起吗
You're sleeping together?
同睡分睡的问题 从你们一相见就困扰着我
I mean, it's been a "will they or won't they" since they met.
各位乡亲 苏菲驾到啦
Hi, everybody. Sophie's here!
瞧我的新狐皮大衣 是双巨乳[双排扣]呢
And look at my new coat. It's double-breasted.
很不错吧
Pretty nice, huh?
是我送的礼物呢
It was a gift from me.
这是他送我的东西里
It's the only thing he ever gave me
唯一不会损坏到我生育能力的东西
that didn't threaten my reproductive health.
我觉得那只狐狸在知道
Think that fox took its own life
自己会被做成什么大衣后 甘愿自尽的
when it saw what kind of coat it was gonna be on.
他为什么会送你这个
What is the occasion?
什么为什么
姐姐火辣 天气寒冷
I'm hot and it's cold.
而且还是我跟奥列格首次玩
And it's also the anniversary of the first time
70式的纪念日
Oleg and I 70ed.
哥哥"功夫"好 "69"升华变70
The way I do it, it's one more than 69.
麦克斯 我刚挂了一通超让人恐慌的电话
Max, I just hung up from a very panicked phone call,
你绝对不敢相信电话中说的事
and you'll never believe what happened.
唱片行那男的打给你 告诉你
The guy from the record store called to say
我有超级淋病[新型性病]吗
I have super gonorrhea?
你真觉得一个被你"睡"过就忘了的男人
You actually think a guy that you don't even remember
会打来告诉我 你有超级淋病吗
called to tell me that you have super gonorrhea?
对啊 我累到真这么觉得
Yes, that's how tired I am.
你是还要让我等多久啊
Are you gonna make me wait forever?
我到底有没得病
Do I have it or not?
才不是超级淋病 只是个超级坏消息而已
It's not super gonorrhea, but it is super-bad news.
这女人刚打来跟我确认她订的
This woman just called to confirm her order
明天要的一千个小蛋糕
for 1,000 cupcakes for tomorrow.
我最近太累 完全忘了这事
I've been so tired, I completely forgot.
我还宁愿得了超级淋病呢
I'd rather have super gonorrhea!
你疯啦
Are you insane?
我们哪可能明天前做好啊
We can't do 1,000 cupcakes by tomorrow.
不行也得行
We have to do it.
不然我们的商誉就付之一炬了
It'll ruin our reputation if we don't.
我知道我们都累翻了 但只要再撑一晚
I know we're tired, but if we stay up all night,
明早10AM我们就能有四千块入袋呢
we'll have $4,000 by tomorrow at 10:00 A.M.
还得是10AM就做好啊
They have to be done by 10:00 A.M.?
我累得脑子不转了 AM是指上午吗
I'm so tired, remind me- is A.M. the morning one?
我们做不了 不可能做到
We can't do it. It's impossible.
我现在脑子一团浆糊 不会算数了
My brain's too foggy to crunch the numbers,
但如果现在开溜 明早一定能完工
but I'm sure it's doable if we leave right now.
我们服务员的工作还没结束呢
We're in the middle of waiting tables.
那我们只好找理由翘班啦
Well, we'll just have to come up with an excuse.
把手给我 弯下腰 装病
Give me your hand, bend over, and pretend to be sick.
肯定能行 我用来翘过八个工作的班
It'll work. I've used this to get out of eight jobs,
六次期末考 以及一次婚礼
six final exams, and one wedding.
阿憨 有紧急病号 卡洛琳病了
Han, we have an emergency. Caroline's sick.
病得很严重 站都站不稳了
She's so sick, she can't even stand up.
我们没办法留下来工作到打烊了
We won't be able to stay and finish our shift.
我们得立刻去急诊室
We have to go right to the emergency room.
还不知道她是什么病
We don't know what's wrong with her,
但她上吐下泻的
but it's coming out of both ends.
说不定会是超级淋病呢 再见
It might be super gonorrhea. Bye.
真是太不幸了
That's so unfortunate.
她们本来今晚终于要"合体"了呢
And on the night they were finally gonna do it.
哇靠 这杯咖啡大得吓人啊
Whoa, those are some big-ass coffees!
没错 1.9升杯呢
Yep, 64-ouncers.
他们说这杯容量比人体的胃还大
They told me they're bigger than the human stomach.
这杯咖啡已经开始发挥作用了
And the coffee's already working,
因为我已经算出 现在是午夜
'cause I figured out if it's midnight now,
而我们得在明早10点交货
we have to be done at 10:00 A.M.
每一批小蛋糕从头到尾需要40分钟
so if it's 40 minutes per batch from beginning to end,
一次能做四打 也就是48个小蛋糕
baking 4 dozen at a time, that's 48 cupcakes
乘以20批 刚好花费9小时
Times 20 trips to the oven, which equals nine hours,
就等于四千块入手
which equals $4,000.
快让我喝两口 看我能不能学会算数
Give me that. Let's see if I can do math too.
出题考我吧
Ask me something.
16乘12
16 times 12.
我还是乖乖享受我的咖啡就好
I'm just going to enjoy my coffee.
你慢慢享用 我去预热烤箱
You enjoy, I'll preheat the oven.
要几度 162摄氏度
What's the temp? 325.
喝了咖啡 再也不担心数学
There, that's the coffee talking.
安迪发了我一张鹿给乌龟喂奶的图
Andy just sent me a picture of a deer nursing a turtle.
这就是它们教导小乌龟
This is why they tell teen turtles
不要乱贴照片上脸书的原因
never to post up on facebook.
我都不知道你俩还在互发短信呢
Oh, I didn't realize you two were still texting.
我们通常都只是在互发
Well, we're mostly just sending pictures
非比寻常的动物友情图而已
of unlikely animal friendships.
你看 这张是熊跟兔子一起睡午觉
See, there's a bear napping with a bunny.
那这个呢
And what's this?
是拉布拉多德利犬跟锦鲤击掌
It's a labradoodle high-fiving a koi fish.
不是挺明摆着的嘛
It's pretty self-explanatory.
不 是图下的字 这个
No, underneath that. This--
"卡洛琳还好吗"
"How's Caroline?"
不是只是"非比寻常动物友情图之友"吗
I thought this was just an unlikely animal friendship.
通常都是啊 但有些短信
It is, mostly, but every other text,
让我觉得他还没放下你呢
I get the idea that maybe he's not over you.
是他甩了我好吗
He's the one who broke up with me.
可能他后悔呢
Well, maybe he regrets it.
你们可能就像克里斯小子与蕾哈娜啊
Maybe you two are like Chris Brown and Rihanna,
少了拳打脚踢与合唱版的
minus the punching and the duet.
其实我挺讶异的
I'm kind of surprised.
我觉得你们俩很配呢
I thought you guys were good together.
安迪很好 而平常呢
Andy is great. And on the surface,
他也总是守护我 支持我
he was there for me and very supportive.
但后来他有点受不了
But then he kind of got fed up
我太注重自己与事业的这件事
when it was so much about me and my career.
直到最后 悲剧发生
And when push came to shove,
他为了自己着想 觉得该放下这段感情
he felt like he had to pull away for his own well-being.
天啊 我们还真是蕾哈娜与克里斯小子
Oh, my God, we are Rihanna and Chris Brown!
而我就是克里斯小子
But I'm Chris Brown.
说到克里斯小子
Speaking of Chris Brown,
我要开始搅拌[痛打]啦
I'm gonna start to batter.
烤箱怎么样了
How's that stove?
温度上来了 但它好摇晃啊
Warm, but it's really wobbly.
它摇摇晃晃 又冒烟[抽烟]
Yeah, it wobbles, it smokes,
有次还烫了我
and one time it burned me.
所以我给它的昵称是"老妈"
That's why I nicknamed it "mom."
烤箱脚下的那块木头是什么
What is this wood thing under the leg?
是垫木
It's the shim.
好像就是它让烤箱不稳的
I think it's making it worse.
别啊 那是来垫烤箱脚的
Don't! That's holding the leg up!
想必你现在明白它的作用了
But I guess you figured that out now.
我不都说是垫木了吗
You heard me say it was the shim!
我哪知道什么是垫木啊
I don't know what a shim is.
我还以为又是个街头词汇之类的
I thought it was just one of those things you say.
那垫木还能是啥意思啊
What did you think it could be?
我还以为是混词之类的啊
I thought it was a cool word blend.
称呼变性人用的"他与她"混合词[音似]
You know, like she/him for a transsexual--a shim.
你觉得有迷你变性人托着我们的炉子吗
You thought a tiny transsexual was holding up our stove?
没错 我累到真这么以为
Yes, Max, I'm that tired.
觉得有一个迷你变性人正托着我们的炉子
I thought a tiny transsexual was holding up our stove.
这下悲剧了 我们家的烤箱也不够大
This is a disaster, and our oven at home's too small.
我们现在怎么办啊
What are we gonna do now?
太好了 你们还在
Oh, good, you're still here.
大家不许走 我们今晚倒霉透了
Don't anybody leave. Our night just got worse.
别再靠近我了 超级淋病妹
Don't come any closer, super gonorrhea!
对不起 我们为了翘班撒谎了
I'm sorry to say we lied to get off our shift.
但我们得在明天前烤出一千个小蛋糕
But we have to bake 1,000 cupcakes by tomorrow,
但我们店里的烤箱坏了 得借用你的
and our oven broke at the shop, and we need to use yours.
你撒谎骗我 现在还要我帮忙啊
You lied to me, and now you want a favor?
是的 阿憨 我们请你帮这个大忙
Yes. Han, we know it's a big favor,
在你眼中可能看起来显得更大
and it probably looks even bigger to you,
但我相信你会原谅我们的谎
but I'm sure you can see past our lie.
如果你真不能原谅 那你就起立
And if you can't, you can get up on that chair,
我让你坐上我肩头玩...
I could put you on our shoulders...
长话超短说 你愿意帮忙吗
Long story abnormally short, will you help us?
你那无数矮子嘲讽惹到我了
Well, those 12 short jokes really primed me.
但好吧 你们用吧
Fine, you can use the oven
其他东西也都随你们用
and any of the supplies you need.
谢谢 小蛋糕真的非做成不可
Thank you. We really need to fill this order.
我留下来帮手吧
I'll stay and help.
我也有些事得"做"
I also had something to fill,
但我还是短信苏菲说我在工作吧
but I'll just text Sophie and tell her I'm working.
我也留下帮忙
I'll help too.
我不会烤东西 但坐着与鼓舞士气很在行
I can't bake, but I can sit and lift the spirits.
只要能有酒[士气]喝就行了
as long as there are spirits.
无限畅饮对吧 阿憨
It's open bar, right, Han?
好吧 我也加入
Okay, I'm in too.
厄尔 给我来个海风鸡尾酒
Earl, make me a sea breeze,
微风就好别太烈
easy on the breezy.
由于我的儿时阴影
You know, because of my childhood,
我对你们现在
I won't be able to process the fact
留下来帮手的好心举动反应无能
that you've all just done something nice for me,
所以如果十年后 我遇见你们时突然大哭
So if I run into you in ten years and start crying,
哭的就是现在这一刻
this is what it's about.
九百个小蛋糕 新鲜出炉
900 and counting. Comin' through.
你想让我放哪
Where do you want them?
这里 就放在史上动作最慢的帮手旁边
Put 'em over here, next to the world's slowest helper.
你裱一个小蛋糕的花比
It took you longer to make that one cupcake
詹姆斯·卡梅隆拍一部《阿凡达》还慢
than it took James Cameron to make Avatar.
这活我干了两分钟
Well, I been doing this for two minutes,
不得不说...
and I have to say...
不适合我
not for me.
你知道我适合干什么吗
But you know what is for me?
再"干"一杯免费白兰地
Another free cognac.
准备好再来一杯海风了吗 小憨憨
Ready for another sea breeze, Han?
等我弄好了再说
Not before I get this right.
而且你不会想看到我两杯海风下肚后的样子
And you don't want to see me on two sea breezes.
会怎么样 你会变成"林赛·蠢憨"吗
What happens, you become Lindsay Lo-Han?
好吧 让我来教你怎么做
Okay, let me show you how it's done.
这样 感觉到了吗 阿憨
There, you feel how that is, Han?
-有吧 -好的
- Uh, yes. - Ok.
现在用力挤那袋"奶油"
Now just squeeze that bag.
很好 再用力点
Good. Little harder.
丢死人了
I'm humiliated.
没关系啦 阿憨
It's okay, Han,
很多男人第一次都会这样
it happens to a lot of guys their first time.
赶紧像别人那样 拿张纸巾
Get yourself a tissue and clean yourself off,
擦擦干净
like everyone else.
阿憨 这活你不用干了
Han, you're off the bag.
我要派你去搅面粉
I'm moving you to batter.
这不是降职 只是你裱花太烂
It's not a demotion, it's just that you stink at this.
我想让你去干点容易的
I wanna give you something easier.
麦克斯 你的围裙弄脏了
Max, you just got that all over your apron.
我来帮你擦干净 我的也脏了
I'll wipe it down. Mine's a mess too.
哇 动作真熟练
Ooh, pretty slick move.
下次想试试脱我的胸罩吗
You wanna try for my bra next?
好啊 宝贝
Yeah, baby,
我来帮你脱胸罩
I'll take off your bra.
那声音是怎么回事
What the hell was that?
怎么了 那是我的男声啊
What? It's my guy voice.
你学男声就是这样啊
That's your go-to guy voice?
日界线新闻节目有保护你这变态的身份吗
Is his identity being protected on Dateline?
那你的男声是什么样
Well, what's your guy voice like?
就现在这样啊
I'm doing it right now.
我要快快地去尿个尿
I'm gonna take a quick pee break.
不知道 或许是你调的酒酒劲太强了
I don't know, I think you might be making the drinks too strong.
我们没有醉 奥列格 只是神志模糊而已
We're not drunk, Oleg, just punchy.
我单纯是喝醉了
I'm just drunk.
大家能留下来陪我们到这么晚 真好
It was so nice of everyone to stay that long.
除了这些 其他的都烤好了
Everything's baked except for those.
我们能搞定的 麦克斯
We've gonna make it, Max.
安迪发给我一张猫咪和海豚的接吻照
Andy sent me a cat and a dolphin kissing.
希望它们不只接吻 我好想看它们爱的结晶
I hope they go all the way. I'm dying to see their baby.
猫豚 棒呆了
A cat-dolphin? Yes!
我觉得这样不好吧
I don't think that's healthy.
如果真的相爱
Well, if they're in love,
那关你屁事啊
it's really none of your business.
为什么大半夜你还给他发短信啊
Why are you texting him in the middle of the night?
老实说 为什么他还没睡
In fact, why is he still up?
他是不是在打听我啊
Is he talking about me?
你看起来不爽
You look upset.
你要我别跟他发短信吗
Do you want me to stop texting him?
不用 没关系
No. It's fine.
只是我累了 活也差不多干完了
It's just I'm tired and we're almost finished,
我现在只想回家
and I just wanna go home.
收到 我热死了
Got it. I'm so hot.
等我先把头发扎起来
Let me just get this hair off my neck.
麦克斯 为什么你今天只戴一只耳环
Max, why are you wearing only one earring?
你瞎说什么 我明明戴的是两只
What are you talking about? I'm wearing two.
奇了怪了
That's weird.
还有一只呢 是不是在我头发里
Where is it? Is it in my hair?
没有啊 是不是掉下来了
No, no. Did it fall down?
快检查下你的咪咪
Yeah, check your boobs.
上次遥控器就是在那发现的
That's where you found the remote.
不在 不在我身上
It's not-it's not anywhere on me.
你最后一次看见它是什么时候
Well, when's the last time you saw it?
我不知道 但肯定在这附近
I don't know, but it couldn't have gone far.
我几乎一整晚都在这里
I was in this area pretty much the whole night.
你是说在面粉糊上方吗
You mean over the batter?
-没有 没有 -没发现 没发现
- No, no, no. - Nothing, nothing, nothing!
- No, no, no, no. - Nothing, nothing, nothing!
-没有 没有 -没发现 没发现
- No, no, no, no, no! - Nothing, nothing, no!
不在这里 那就意味着
It's not here, which means
那只耳环在其中一个做好的小蛋糕里
it's in one of those already-baked cupcakes.
来吧 我们得开始逐个掰开找
Let's go. We have to start pulling these apart.
来真的啊 拜托 别小题大作嘛
Really? Come on, don't be ridiculous.
最坏的情况不过也是 在一千个小蛋糕中
Look, worst-case scenario, one of the 1,000 cupcakes
有一个里面有只耳环
has an earring in it.
跟客人说是惊喜礼物就好啦
We'll tell them it's a surprise.
不行 最坏的情况是有人吃到那个小蛋糕
No, the worst-case scenario is someone bites into it,
把嘴唇弄破了 然后把我们告上法庭
rips their lip open, and sues us.
随便他们告 反正我们没钱赔
Let them sue us. We don't have any money.
所以我们就会进监狱
And that's why we'll go to jail.
没错 我会被关进大牢
Yep, I'll be locked up raw
然后被迫做别人的女玩物
and forced to be someone's girlfriend.
我在监狱外已经是个坏女友了
I mean, I'm a bad girlfriend out of prison.
跟监狱大姐大在一起 能好过吗
It's not gonna be any easier with big joan.
淡定
Calm down.
如果我们进监狱 我来做你的女友
If we go to prison, I'll be your girlfriend.
直到有更性感的妞进来取代我
Until someone hotter comes along,
监狱里都是这样
'cause that's the way it goes in prison.
开始找吧
Start looking.
我才不要捏烂我辛苦做的九百个小蛋糕
I am not going to smash 900 cupcakes.
那我们只好全部重做啦
Then we'll just have to start over.
不要 我宁愿搭个顺风车去西部
Oh, no, I would rather hitch a ride west
然后跟别的女人共事一夫
and become a sister-wife.
这太疯狂了 就不能发短信
This is crazy. Can't I just text them
告诉他们 这活我们干不了吗
and tell them we can't do the job?
不 你不能这样做 我们需要这笔钱
No, you can't text them. We need the money.
别老发什么破短信了
And stop with all the texting.
或许如果你不是整天想着
Maybe if you were thinking less about
跟我的前男友发短信
texting with my ex-boyfriend,
你就不会弄丢你的耳环
you wouldn't have lost your earring in the first place.
这话你早就该说了
You should have just said it.
你不爽我跟安迪发短信
You have a problem with me texting Andy.
我才没有不爽
I do not have a problem with it!
很好 因为他也是我的朋友
Oh, good, 'cause he's my friend too.
你不觉得你对最好朋友
You'd think your loyalty to your best friend
和生意伙伴的忠诚度要比
and business partner would be more important
那些白痴的动物友情重要得多吗
than some stupid animal friendship!
我是说...
I mean...
我真吃惊这种话得我亲自说出口 麦克斯
I'm surprised I even have to tell you that, Max.
这可是"闺蜜法则"
It's kind of girl code.
老娘太累 不想听什么狗屁"闺蜜法则"
Oh, I am way to tired to hear "girl code."
别说了
Shut it down.
闺蜜法则 麦克斯
Girl code, Max.
闺蜜法则
Girl code.
闭嘴 卡洛琳
Shut up, Caroline.
闭嘴
Shut up!
我都不屑于对此做出反应了
I'm not even gonna dignify that with a response.
没错 这就是我的目的 贱人
Yeah, that was the goal, bitch.
我没空跟你吵架
I don't have time for this.
我得在这一千个小蛋糕里
I have to find an earring that you lost
找出你不见的那只耳环 贱人
in one of these thousand cupcakes, bitch!
是你忘记告诉我要做这一千个小蛋糕
The thousand cupcakes that you forgot to tell me about!
闺蜜法则就是说 当你的闺蜜
And the girl code means that when a girl
跟别人分手时
breaks up with someone,
你不会跟她们的男友搅和在一起
you don't interfere with their boyfriend,
因为你的闺蜜想跟他保持距离
because she needs some distance.
那你为什么不在14小时前
Well, why didn't you tell me that
我问你的时候告诉我
When I asked you 14 hours ago?
麦克斯 我收到你的短信
Hey, Max. I got your text.
我是来帮忙的
I'm here to help.
那条是在闺蜜法则出现前发的
Um, that was a pre-girl-code text.
在厄尔醉倒 我把小憨憨弄哭后
I thought we maybe needed a backup
我觉得我们可能需要个后备帮手
after Earl passed out and I made Han cry.
安迪 在我人生中内疚之事的榜单里
Andy, on the list of things I feel guilty about in life,
半夜叫你来帮忙这件事
calling you to help in the middle of the night
排名第二
is number two.
本来能荣登榜首
It would be number one
但榜首是那个我因为想更早进入
if I hadn't pushed that girl down the stairs
98度乐队的音乐会 而被我推下楼梯的女生
to get into the 98 degrees concert before her.
那可是98度啊
Well, it was 98 degrees.
人必需得死啊
People had to die.
好了 别装没事开玩笑了
Okay, let's stop all this joking
认真说说我来这里的真正原因吧
and get down to why I really came here.
求你了 卡洛琳 爱我吧
Come on, Caroline, love me.
你刚是说 "卡洛琳 爱我吧"吗
Did you just say, "Caroline, love me"?
不 我是说 "卡洛琳 套我吧"
No, I said, "Caroline, glove me."
要多卑微才会求人说 "爱我吧"
what kind of loser would say, "Love me"?
除非你真爱我
Unless you do.
你过得怎么样
So how you doing?
还行
I'm okay.
就是有点累
A little tired.
我最近常常想起你
You know, I've been thinking about you a lot.
自从我们分手后 我一直在想你
Pretty much all the time since we broke up.
或许我对你沉迷于工作
Um, maybe I overreacted to your whole
这件事有点反应过激
obsession with work thing, you know?
你之所以凌晨4点还在这里
Well, you are here at 4:00 A.M.
是因为我得在4小时内做出一千个小蛋糕
'cause I needed help making 1,000 cupcakes in four hours.
或许有人会称其为"沉迷"
One might call that obsessive.
有人会
One might.
又或者人人都会这么说
Or pretty much everyone might.
安迪
And, Andy,
即使深知我们之间不可能了
just know that even though it didn't work out,
但我真的"套"你
I do glove you.
我也"套"你
I glove you too.
现在赶紧在烤糊之前 把小蛋糕都拿出来
Now, get the cupcakes out before they burn.
我没有精力再重做一遍
I don't have the energy to do this all again.
我甩了的工作狂女友现身了
Ah, there's the girl I broke up with.
外面一切东西都准备好了
Everything's ready to go out there.
我的手今晚进过的箱子
I've had my hands in more boxes tonight
比免费诊所妇科医生的手进过的阴道还多
than a gynecologist at a free clinic.
没这么好笑吧
It's not that funny.
等你27个小时不睡觉
Stay up another 27 hours,
这会是你这辈子听过最好笑的一句话
it'll be the funniest damn thing you ever heard.
都结束了
Well, that's the end of it.
是啊 结束了
Yeah, I think it is.
麦克斯 我说的不只是小蛋糕
Max, I'm talking about more than the cupcakes.
是啊 我能从你布莱德利·库珀式的音调里听出
Yeah, I could tell by your Bradley Cooper tone.
怎么了 你们俩彻底不可能了吗
So what, it's not gonna work out between you two?
是啊
No.
我觉得我们必须分手
And I think we have to break up.
我以为你俩早就分了啊
I thought you already broke up.
不 我是在说我和你
No, I'm talking about you and me.
你要甩了我啊
You're dumping me?
上一个甩我的男人
Wow, last guy who dumped me,
我把他的房子烧了 然后搬走
I burned down his house and moved.
还想继续这个话题吗
Still wanna continue this conversation?
麦克斯 这样不行
Max, it wouldn't work.
我会一直跟你打听卡洛琳
I would always be asking you about Caroline.
我明白 这样很奇怪
Look, I get it, it's weird.
人们一般不会跟自己朋友的前任成为朋友
People don't usually stay friends with their friend's ex,
可是猫咪一般也不会跟海豚成为朋友啊
But then, cats don't usually become friends with dolphins.
可有时 缘分就是这么奇妙
But sometimes, for no apparent reason, it happens.
是啊 我只希望我跟
Yeah, I just wish I was as grown up
猫或海豚一样成熟
as a cat or a dolphin.
我懂你意思
I hear ya.
那接下来是什么 分手短信吗
So what's next, breakup text?
不要 发了之后就会有复合短信
Nah, that's just gonna lead to makeup text,
然后我们就这么恶性循环下去
and then we're back in a vicious cycle.
好吧 那我只好去你家一趟
All right, I'll just stop by your place,
拿回我的CD和T恤
pick up my cds, my t-shirts,
还有留在你家的三千块
and the 3 grand I left there.
麦克斯 你从来没去过我家
Max, you've never been to my place.
瞧 这就是我要跟你分手的原因
See, this is why I'm breaking up with you--
你个骗子
You're a liar.
索赔法院见 伙计
See you in small claims court, bub.
我们做到了 麦克斯
Well, we did it, Max.
我们赚到了4千块
We made $4,000.
关于我和安迪
And as far as Andy and I go,
我觉得我们像现在这样正好
I think we're in the right place,
因为当他说他分手后
because when he said he'd been thinking about me
每分每秒都在想我
since the breakup,
我才意识到自己每分每秒想的都是小蛋糕
I realized I'd only been thinking about the cupcakes.
天啊 拜托把嘴闭上
Oh, please, god, shut up.
谢谢 我的嘴也超级想休息
Thank you. I was dying to shut up.
是顾客发来的短信
Look, it's a text from the place.
他们很喜欢我们的小蛋糕
They loved the cupcakes.
慢着 为什么你的手机会在我的围裙里
Wait, why do I have your phone in my apron?
不可能 我的手机是放在我的围裙里
No, my phone was in my apron.
除非我当时擦完围裙后
Unless I handed you the wrong apron
错把我的递给你了
after I wiped them down.
什么
What?
果然
你的耳环
Oh...Your earring.
它一直在我这里
I had it in there the whole time.
我们俩白痴
Oh, we're idiots!
虽说是两种完全不同类型的白痴
We're two very different kinds of idiots,
但我们都是白痴
but we're idiots.
然而不知何故 我们俩超搭
And yet, somehow we work.
我们就像非比寻常的动物朋友
We're the most unlikely animal friends.
我是不知道啦 但我给你喂奶的照片
I don't know about that, but a picture of me nursing you
绝对会在网络上爆红
would definitely go viral.
-晚安 -晚安
- Good night. - Good night.
你要去哪里
Where you going?
我累得没力气把床弄下来了
I'm too tired to pull my bed down.
我要跟你一起睡
I'm sleeping with you.
不行 你可是有超级淋病
No, you're not. You have super gonorrhea.